The first story time Tom I want to get
into is the story of SpaceX. So Elon
isn't just trying to eliminate dead
zones. He is trying to literally become
your phone company. And when this
announcement was made, let me tell you
how scary it was for Verizon. Verizon
stock dropped 7.3%. AT&T dropped 7.8%.
T-Mobile dropped 7%. He agreed to buy
roughly $8 billion worth of nationwide
800 megga megahertz lowband spectrum
from grain management. Then the deal
gives SpaceX up to 14 megahertz of of
paired spectrum and comes on top of
prior spectrum acquisitions including
roughly $19.6 billion tied to Echoar
Spectrum purchases. SpaceX also has FCC
approval for 15,000 Stellion Gen 2
Starling mobile uh uh constellation. So
all of this stuff means what? This isn't
a phone company. So, they haven't yet
announced that they're gonna have their
own Tesla competing with iPhone or
competing with Android or all the other
phones that are out there. This is
service. So, he's going to service
first. So, you ever have a pocket where
you drive and I don't know if you guys
got this or not. Every time I drive and
I go up to Palm Beach
and I pass by Bokeh, like right between
Bokeh and Boon, there's about five
minutes that AT&T service isn't good. or
if I fly out to uh go to LA and I'm on
the 210 freeway, certain pockets of it,
certain areas in Dallas, you don't have
good service. Well, with this thing with
Starlink, we're on a jet. I'm on a jet.
We're going from here to Vegas, we're
having phone calls. We're doing Zoom
calls. We're we're the internet is
ridiculous. And we're like, Tom, what
the hell is going on with this jet?
Starlink. Now, when you go on flights,
you're like, well, we're so sorry. The
internet is bad. When they say they're
Starling quality is great. By the way,
cable cable TV internet infiniti sucks
right now. Starling's going to come and
say, "Don't worry about these guys. They
are about to take out a lot of different
markets out there. Specifically, these
companies like Verizon, AT&T, and
T-Mobile are shivering of what Starlink
and SpaceX could turn into. So, Tom, how
worried should they be?"
>> Well, they should be very worried, and
I'm going to tell you the words that did
it. So Elon Musk is going to take
Starlink and bring it all the way down
and provide internet service. That's not
really news because remember uh a
certain country um uh Zalinski was
begging for Starlink to get internet to
the people and to its military. So
that's been coming. Here's what freaked
everybody out. What you just read about
is the Spectrum deal. Exactly as you
said. And then this these words, this
will be coupled to an advanced
terrestrial deployment. Advanced
terrestrial. You know what terrestrial
means, Vinnie?
>> Earth. So, this will be connected to an
advanced Earth deployment, which means
that it's not just Starlink, it's also a
terrestrial network with all of the
billions of dollars he's got to work
with and with the old uh T-Mobile uh
spectrum. When those words came across
the T-Mobile spectrum and connected to a
terrestrial an advanced terrestrial
deployment, what happened then is, you
know, Grain's own legal advisor flipped
out and said, "Wait a minute, that
service reaching customers from both
space and Earth." So, in other words, if
there's dead zones, like maybe you're
too deep inside of a building for
Starlink outside, don't worry about it
because they're also going to supplement
it. So, when you put those two things
together, Pat, that's what freaked out
all those stocks. Everybody goes, "Wait
a minute. He's not just going to put a
blanket from space. He's going to fill
in gaps in major cities and concrete
buildings from the Earth side." And he's
doing with the spectrum. When both of
those things came out, boom, all the
futures, what you saw, the stocks went
down, they only went down 7%. Why did
they go down more than that, Vinnie?
Because in every stock, you have today's
value based on your business and how
valuable you are today and a speculation
of the future. That's when you'll see
Jensen Wang says he's going to sell
another 9,000 chips to Google. Nvidia
jumps a point. Yeah,
>> that money hasn't hit the bank. They're
talking about selling in the future. But
guess what? Nvidia stock goes up on
future speculation and future business.
Guess what? Verizon and these guys, the
7% that just went down, that's part of
their future business. And the question
is going to be, you know, how quickly
can Elon do this? But you know what?
Elon Musk just became he's sort of a
combination of Thomas Edison and EF
Hutton. Do you remember EF Hutton? When
EF Hutton talks,
>> people listen. Remember that old thing?
>> Of course. Yeah.
>> So, he's sort of Thomas Thomas Edison
and EF Hutton.
>> Well, I would tell you this. Here's a
question. Can we run a poll on the back?
This is the question I got for you
folks. If you knew those dead zones that
you deal with with AT&T, with Verizon,
with T-Mobile, and if you have any, post
in the comments section if you have your
do you know the dead zones, what areas
you have bad service? Name the areas
that you get bad service and who you're
with. Well, well, here it's not that
bad, but like for instance, my sister's
driving on the 405 to LAX cuz she works
at the Space Force. Pat, there's a
there's a stretch of road for
>> and it's not a bridge. She's not going
through a bridge or a tunnel.
>> No, it's it's on the 405 from the 101.
Completely done. And then when they go
into the hill with Who's her phone with?
>> I don't I don't text her while she's not
up at text. Who do you have any dead
zones yourself that you drive through
>> here in South Florida? Yeah. Always
around Hollywood near the airport.
>> Near the airport. Do you experience
anytime? And you're AT&T. I'm also AT&T.
>> Absolutely. Uh when I go into my
backyard to talk to you, you'll say,
"Tom, I can't hear you. Tom, what's
going on?"
>> Wow. Right there.
>> And that's when I I always say, "I'm
sorry, Pat." I walk back toward the
front of my house, the back of my house,
everything there. Coral Ridge on the
back.
>> So, if if you knew that 100% of those
dead zones are going to be gone, would
you switch to Starling?
>> I would paint my roof with Elon, start
here.
>> Are you being sarcastic or serious?
>> I am being serious. Start here.
>> Is that big of a problem for you? where
when you're a businessman and you're a
saleserson, you're on the phone with a
client, you're trying to confirm.
There's nothing more annoying than
>> call drops, then you're down the street
from the house, a business person's on
the phone all the time. Not if you're a
social media person, but a business
person that's calling talking all the
time, that's a problem for me. Can we
run a poll? Here's the poll. If Starlink
eliminated 100% of the dead zones, would
you leave AT&T, Verizon, and whoever
you're with for Starlink? Yes. No, I'm
just curious to know what people would
say.
>> My sister's uh My sister's AT&T.
>> She's also AT&T.
>> I've been with AT&T. I switched from
AT&T to Verizon for two weeks. You know
why I switched back to AT&T? One
feature. Verizon would only let you do
three-way with two people.
>> Okay.
>> And AT&T allows me to do three-way calls
with five, six, seven people. And by the
way, AT&Tell
>> AT&T has screwed up their three-way
calls lately. It's been pretty bad
lately. But something tells me AT&T's
three-ways work at Cornell still right
now.
>> And let me ask you a question, Matt. So,
so here's my goal because we we're
always learning. Tom still loves that
one. So, okay. So, he's obviously this
is one of the reasons remember like I
think it was like a month ago or two
months ago I was asking man it's like
every week Elon's launching something
and like you don't even pay attention
every day they're launching and
launching launching launching. This is
probably one of the reasons obviously
but my my question is as the competitors
what is what is AT&T because think about
it how are their satellites up there Pat
that goes through our government. Who's
launching the AT&T, Verizon, you know,
Sprint? Who puts all their stuff into
the into the orbit? Tom, is is it a deal
with NASA? How are they launching? How
how is how are they getting their stuff
up there? And how are they going to
>> SpaceX is putting it up there?
>> No. What I'm saying is how is uh all the
other carriers doing it? They have to go
through NASA and somebody else.
>> No, no, no. The the other carriers right
now are terrestrial networks.
>> Okay. So, it's not even out there.
>> It's all those triangular.
>> Okay. So, it's not even out there. So
he's he's
>> Yeah, there there there have been
things. Intelsat had some stuff up
there. There was there was some services
that were up there, but they were like
emergency services or marine services.
Okay, if you've ever take a look at um
satphone. Hey guys, go look up a thing.
Just go look up on um satellite phone
2025 and you're going to see it's a
square phone with a big antenna on it.
It works very well for emergencies. It's
very expensive, the satones. And um
yeah, see there? Yeah,
>> they're very expensive to use, but
they're great if you're out there on on
the water and you have an emergency.
Well, now he's like, "Yeah, don't worry
about that. Let's just make it easy."
>> Bro, you're going to be on a plane. You
can make phone calls. I mean, this is
the for business people. This is
incredible.
>> So, let me ask you a question, though.
As as the comp as the other guys, what
do you do to try to compete with him?
How?
>> It's too late.
>> Okay. That's what I was going to say.
>> So, the only thing the only thing is is
people don't like change. And there's
about an age you get to where you don't
like to change products
>> because it's just habitual. It takes you
a while to change away from certain
things. There's people still that get
physical newspapers that come in.
>> Their age doesn't start with two.
>> No, it doesn't.
>> But their age may start with six.
>> Okay. So, there's certain people that
have been with AT&T Verizon for a long
time that they'll switch. I'm not
talking about Tom. This is not a Tom
thing because Tom is a technology guy.
He'll switch with anybody that's making
it. So, then this is this becomes the
next question. The next question is the
following. Sequencing. Elon is all about
sequencing.
>> First, put all the chargers everywhere.
Yeah.
>> And then know that all your competitors
need to use your chargers.
>> Charger.
>> And then, you know, hey, come on, pay
up. You know, you're going to need me.
>> They cut deals with all of them. And
they even modified their plugs to work
on.
>> So, here's the question. What is the
likelihood, Tom, that sequencing first
beat AT&T, beat Verizon, beat those
guys, two, come out with a Tesla phone?
What's the likelihood he comes out with
a Tesla phone? extremely there was
number
>> uh I I think that it's 70% and rising
every minute because if you look there
has been a Tesla prototype or like an X
prototype
and a uh I think you guys find it guys
like
>> Tom keep talking he'll look
they've done their they've done their
their prototypes on it and people have
seen there's been the Tesla phone and
there's been
>> so you think 70% they'll come out with
something
>> I don't think this is a teaser I think
this This is This is on the bench.
>> So, you know what this means? You know
You know who this is embarrassing for?
>> Yeah. This is I think this is not just
>> No. You know who this is embarrassing
for?
>> One company. Nope. Keep going. You're
close. One company. This is embarrassing
for
>> Apple. What? So, so what what Apple is
doing is
Apple could have done this. They didn't
do this. Apple stayed on the phone side.
And Apple's flywheel, if you think on
the flywheel side,
Elon is expanding his flywheel. What is
he doing with the flywheel?
>> Buy the Tesla, buy Starlink, buy a
phone. The phone talks to the car. He's
going to add his flywheel and expand it
where somebody who owns a Tesla. Like
yesterday, I'm talking to a client Matt
Matthew. And the entire time he's
talking, it's a two-hour engagement with
this client that I met through Manct.
He's I think he's about to sell his
business for multi-billion dollars. very
successful client of ours that we've
been doing engagements for for a while.
And
he's talking to me sitting like this and
for about the first minute I'm like,
"What is this guy doing?" I see trees
moving, everything moving. I said, "Are
you in a Uber?" He says, "No." I said,
"Are you in a Tesla?" The car is
driving. He says, "Yeah." I said,
"You're in a driver's seat." He says,
"Yes." For two hours he's in a driver's
seat like this. He's just talking to him
in cars, taking a place.
>> Oh, he's on full self drive.
>> He's on full self drive. So, what what
what Elon is doing is he's building a
full-on flywheel that's going to get
people to not be able to leave Tesla or
have to go to get this phone if they
switch and they do what we think is
about to be done. Adam, your thoughts?
>> I was actually just going to go to this
flywheel thing because I want to give a
shout out to BDC. You've been talking
about the concept of a flywheel for a
few years now. In one of the articles,
it talks about Elon's flywheel and
Humberto, I sent you that if you're with
us. It says this move could with SpaceX
could potentially fuel his flywheel
between launch Starlink and AI. And this
is what I had AI basically build out.
This is Elon's flywheel. It would seem
where SpaceX launches the rockets.
Starlink uh has the satellite internet.
They this mobile company you're talking
about, the likelihood of it basically
being built is pretty certain at this
point. connects the phones, AI or they
call SI these days with the intelligence
and that leads to revenue and scale and
then it all goes back again. This
concept of a flywheel, you've been
talking about this for years. It looks
like Elon is implementing what
>> power power. By the way, the poll says
uh if Starlink eliminated 100% of the
dead zones, would you switch? 86% said
yes.
>> And the 14% that said no are uh the same
people that want social security to
continue. It's it's a it's a it's a very
the people that were are going to want
to switch. He's not just going to give
you better service. This guy's creative
enough to think about what other things
to do. By the way, for some of you guys
that are watching this, if you're think
you're a business person, you want to
get if you're moving forward nowadays
and you don't have a moat with your
company, you're making a massive mistake
cuz the market is very very competitive
and it's moving very very fast. If you
run a business, you want to find out how
to identify a mode for your business and
create your own flywheel. We do this for
a living with different business owners
from around the world. Go to
beddavid.com, fill out the information
below, schedule a time with one of our
consultants, have a call, and uh we'll
we'll sit down, have a strategy session
with you. We do this regularly. But but
the point is, what's next?
>> That's all I was going to ask.
>> What's next with this guy? Okay. What's
next? This guy
>> is is almost building such a massive
thing that every world I'm talking to
>> a chief of staff of a world leader
leader who's in the middle of a war
right now. And one of their main
concerns is the relationship with Iran,
not not Trump.
Because the way the guy described it, he
says, "We know Trump won't be here for
two more years. We know Elon's going to
be a problem for the next 20, 30 years.
>> So, we better get on." So, he is almost
becoming I hate to say this in a and you
got to be this could go very ugly, very
nasty as well. said this two years ago.
>> You know, depending on where his core
is, cuz the core is
>> he is be he is slowly becoming the world
leader of all presidents.
>> You don't have a choice.
>> They got to come to him. He doesn't need
to go to them.
>> They So, forget about like, hey, I'm the
42nd president of the United States.
Like, okay, you all report to me
>> and and you all need what I have to
offer because I'm doing a better job
than the government is doing. If he
builds this into that, listen, this is a
very very uh different direction this
could go to. If the guy's got any evil
tendencies in the inside,
>> yeah,
>> just you know what I'm saying?
>> But but thank but for for what it for
the face value right now, I love that
he's at least leaning on the
conservative mindset of all this woke
nonsense, especially the stuff that
happened with his son daughter now. And
and but look at the flywheel I just did.
Ready for this? rockets, SpaceX, Boring
Company, drilling into everything. Uh,
Neurolink, Tesla, Cell phones in the
future, robots, X, Twitter to X. He's
literally taking over. And I'm telling
you right now, if he turns sour, Tom, if
he gets pissed off,
>> it's it could go ugly very, very
quickly.
>> Very fast.
>> Very quickly.
>> You know, you brought up Apple. There's
something very interesting. Uh, the
Vision Pro is their mixed reality
headset. you know, like kids and gaming
and you and me can go into Facebook with
and all that crap, right? Do you know
what the last major product category was
before that? Because that's a new
category. They've never done those
before was AirPods. Do you know what
what year AirPods was?
>> I mean, that's at least 5 years ago. At
least
>> 2000. You're right. 2016. It's 10 years.
>> And then before that, it was the Apple
Watch 2015.
>> Apple is not looking good right now.
>> So to this is the point you made, Pat.
2015 watch, 2016 AirPods, 2024 Vision
Pro, and now 2026 next year, they're
going to come out with Home Hub. Okay,
fine. But that's hardly
>> that's hardly like a ma major category.
>> You you know, you know, I'm talking to a
a couple publishers right now about
writing a book specifically on flywheel.
We've talked about that because I talked
about this at the vault, I don't know,
two or three years ago. Yeah.
>> We indirectly build a flywheel in PHP.
We build a flywheel that eventually
you're like, "Hey, you can choose to
leave, but good luck having the format
that we have put together. It's not easy
to create."
>> But you you you know, you you want to be
able to do that. Um I think right now if
you were to score the most powerful
flywheel in the world, I would still put
Apple number one.
>> I would put Amazon number two, okay?
Because they they have some But I'm
telling you, very quickly Elon's
flywheel could pass everybody up very
quickly. And some people may even put
him right now ahead of uh Amazon Bezos
as a flywheel. It could change.
>> What is Jeff Bezos's flywheel?
>> He's got a he's got a massive flywheel
of what Amazon does. And then he's got
the servers on the other end with uh
AWS.
>> AWS, you know, he's got he's got so many
different things going on, but uh Disney
was a great flywheel, but they were top
10 flywheel. They've been screwing up
the last few years. Hopefully the new
>> When did you learn the concept of a
flywheel? because I didn't hear you talk
about this
>> 25 years ago when I'm selling insurance.
One of my leaders told me, you know, you
want to be able to create a centers of
influence relationships. And I'm like,
centers of influence. He says, yes. So
then I said, centers of influence, what
does that really mean? So you're trying
to sell insurance. I'm 23 years old. I
build a relationship with this guy named
Jamie Heap. I went in an interview with
him at 21 years old. He's probably going
to watch this and I was so impressed
with him. I don't want to work for his
company. I was leaving Morgans. I was
leaving BS and he was one of the guys I
interviewed him. I liked them. And so,
you know, so I I sat there and I said, I
need to build relationships that are
feeding me leads.
>> So, I went and built 25 relationships
with performers that I knew I could
never get to become insurance agents,
but they were great relationship. One
guy, one guy's name was Eli Daffish,
another guy's name was Jamie H. It was
all these like 25 guys, and every time I
would take him out every quarter, I
would go have lunch with him. I would
take him and I would take the bill
myself because I'm honored that you're
giving me your time. And I would always
hand him a book and I wouldn't ask him
for anything. I'm like, "How can I help
you? How can I help? What do you need
from me?" Eventually, not all of them
did anything for me, but eventually some
of them are like, "You would benefit
from talking to this guy. You would
benefit from talking to that guy." Eli
Daffish gave me 600 names. One of the
names he gave me led to another guy that
led to another guy led to me making $50
million off of one of the contacts that
he introduced me to. Jamie He introduced
me to a guy that ended up being my
branch guy, compliance guy for six,
seven years and he was phenomenal at
what he did. So that became a flywheel
that I knew every month someone's going
to give me a good lead or good referral
that's going to turn into something.
Dudley, he needed something from me.
Dudley introduced me to Tom Ellsworth
and I don't meet Tom Ellsworth. Life
would be a lot more peaceful, but he
introduced he introduced me to Tom
Ellsworth and you wouldn't be as rich
introduced. Let's have a respect for the
money. introduced me to Matt Sapala. Tom
is one of my three best friends in the
world I have right now, right? Because
of Dudley. So, but those are those are
the relationship that you build and that
was a small flywheel for an insurance
guy. I'm a nobody. I'm just trying to
build
>> Did you call it a flywheel then? When
did you learn the word flywheel?
>> Probably in the last 15 years, 10 years.
It's not like
>> But I didn't hear you use the word
flywheel until
>> Adam, you haven't heard me use a lot of
different words. You know, but
>> I've seen I've seen garuk.
dalination,
>> but
>> I've seen a lot of words from you, sir.
>> That's never going to go away on
dissalination.
>> But so that was one of them that we did.
And uh so yeah, when I tell you it's
going to go, it's going to go because it
comes with a certificate of authenticity
and the sticker hologram that tells you
this is limited edition and there's only
a hundred of them. Couple different
types of coins that we launched for the
250 year anniversary that we have. This
I have a bit coin collection in my
house. a Bitcoin collection and I bought
coins for many, many years and I just
set them aside and I sit on them and
somehow someway years later I find that
I 100x the valuation or whatever it is.
But I want you to watch this clip and if
you're somebody that say collects unique
things, this may be something you may
want to buy. Set it aside, put it in
your safe and don't think about it for a
decade or two. Go for it.
>> Some moments in history happen once and
some are worth holding on to forever. To
commemorate 250 years of America, Future
Looks Bright presents a collection built
to become part of history. One Troy
ounce of.999
fine silver, individually numbered, only
100 made. A limited keepsake for those
who value history, collectibility, and
the meaning behind the moment. Own a
piece of America's 250th because the
future looks bright.
>> Oh,
>> yes. And so to go get these, let me put
the link below if you can because
there's different kinds of coins.
Roberto, if you can go to flb.com, you
can order both of them. So when you go
on FLB.com, make sure to go to coin and
then you'll find the coins. Order them.
You will see these. For some of you that
are watching this that didn't get a
chance to get it. You will need to go to
eBay to get them because they're going
to sell out fairly quickly because these
are limited edition. And they come in a
case like this numbered with the
hologram. And again, this is something
you buy, you set aside, and uh you save
for yourself. Again, go to fob.com,
search the word coin, you'll find a
coin. If you want to add other stuff to
it as well, you can. All right. If you
enjoy this video, you want to watch more
videos like this, click here. And if you
want to watch the entire podcast, click
here.